onthebright.com 2017-07-15

# Privacy Policy - Onthebright.com

**What information do we keep?**

We keep your information when you register on our site, you subscribe to our Newsletter or fill out a form.

In any case, you may be asked to enter your full name, email address, mailing address and phone number. This, always taking into consideration that you can visit our site anonymously.

Google and other associated providers, use cookies to serve ads on the site. Google uses the DART cookie that allows you to serve ads to users based on your visit to sites and other sites on the Internet. Users can disable the use of the DART cookie through the Google ad.

**What do we use this information for?**

The information we obtain can be used in the following ways:

To personalize your experience.- Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.

To improve our website.- We continually strive to improve our content offering based on your information and feedback.

To improve customer service.- Your information helps us respond more effectively to your customer service requests and support needs.

To process the transactions.- Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or delivered to any other company for any reason, without your consent, except when there is a particular purpose to deliver some product purchased or requested service .

To manage a contest, promotion or surveys.

To send periodic emails.- The email address you provide us, can be used to receive news from time to time, as well as updates and information related to a product or service, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the security of your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. In addition, the information is encrypted and the database is accessible only by authorized persons and with the special rights of access to such systems, who are obliged to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (cookies are small files that a site or your service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive via the web browser (if you have it enabled.) This allows the sites or systems of the service providers to recognize your browser, Capture and recall certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, track advertising, and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so we can provide better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract third-party services to help us better understand our site visitors. These service providers are not authorized to use the information collected, unless they help us to realize and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to third parties?**

We do not sell, exchange or transfer to third parties your personal data. This does not include the trusted third parties who assist us in the operation of our website, provided that such parties commit to keep the information confidential. We may also disclose your information when we believe it is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce the policies of our site or to protect our property and safety.

**Compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to comply with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Therefore, we will not distribute your personal information to third parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to your information at any time by entering, if applicable, your control panel and going to the “Edit Profile “or request their withdrawal from the Newsletter when they so wish.

**Privacy Policy Online only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Feelingly**

By using our site, you accept our privacy policy of the website.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Send us a message**

If there are any questions about this privacy policy, you can contact us using the following information.

4045 Beverly Glen,

Sherman Oaks, CA 91423

United States
